Finding Aid for the Lloyd Bochner Scripts PASC.0116
UCLA Library Special Collections
Lloyd Bochner scripts
1960-1992
UCLA Library Special Collections
Bochner, Lloyd
PASC.0116
11 Linear Feet (28 boxes)
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
General
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 997094113606533
Biography
Bochner was born in Canada, July 29, 1924; the actor has appeared in numerous films and television series, including "Hong Kong" (1960-61), "The Richard Boone Show" (1963-64), and "Dynasty."
Scope and Content
Collection consists primarily of television scripts related to the career of actor Lloyd Bochner. Contains a variety of titles including "The Richard Boone Show" (1963-64), "Hong Kong" (1960-61), and "Dynasty" (1980-82). Includes annotated scripts, call sheets, and other production related items. Also includes scripts for motion pictures (2) and several radio programs.
Organization
Arranged in the following series:
Television series
Motion pictures
Miniseries
Radio
Made for TV movies
Miscellaneous
Actors -- United States -- Archives; Bochner, Lloyd, 1924-2005--Archives
- TELEVISION SERIES
  - A-TEAM, THE
    - BEVERLY HILLS ASSAULT. Script dated 2/26/85. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ABC'S WIDE WORLD OF MYSTERY
    - NURSE KILLER, THE. Script dated 10/28/74. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - AMAZING SPIDER MAN, THE
    - DARK SIDE OF DR. MOON, THE. Script dated 1/12/78. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - DARK SIDE OF DR. MOON, THE. Script dated 1/30/78. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - BARBARY COAST
    - I'M FROM MISSOURI. Script dated 8/11/75. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - BARNABY JONES
    - DOUBLE VENGEANCE. Script dated 6/11/75. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - LOOSE CONNECTION, THE. Script dated 2/1/73. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - BATTLESTAR GALACTICA
    - BALTAR'S ESCAPE. Script dated 2/21/79. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - GREETINGS FROM EARTH. Script dated 2/8/79. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - BEWITCHED
    - MARRIAGE WITCH'S STYLE. Script dated 12/12/68. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - BIG VALLEY, THE
    - TIME AFTER MIDNIGHT, THE. Script dated 8/2/67. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - BIONIC WOMAN, THE
    - BIO-FEEDBACK. Script dated 11/11/76. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - BJ AND THE BEAR
    - GIRLS ON THE HOLLYWOOD HIGH, THE. Script dated 1/21/80. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - GIRLS ON THE HOLLYWOOD HIGH, THE. Script dated 1/17/80. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - BOB HOPE PRESENTS THE CHRYSLER THEATRE
    - MURDER IN THE FIRST. Script dated 8/12/64. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - WAR AND ERIC KURTZ, THE. Script dated 11/10/64. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - WAR AND ERIC KURTZ, THE. Script dated 12/2/64. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - WAR AND ERIC KURTZ, THE. Script dated 12/8/64. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - BOLD ONES, THE: DOCTORS, THE
    - EMERGENCY. Script dated 9/13/71. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - BONANZA
    - PRINCE, THE. Script dated 12/30/66. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - BRADDOCK
    - Script dated 11/25/66. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - BRANDED
    - 10,000 FOR DURANGO. Script dated 9/20/65. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - TEST, THE. Script dated 12/24/64. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - BRONK
    - BAD BLOOD. Script dated 12/26/75. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - CAIN'S HUNDRED
    - LOBBYIST, THE. Script dated 2/26/62. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - CANNON
    - BITTER LEGION. Script dated 8/3/72. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - TRIANGLE OF TERROR. Script dated 2/13/74. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - CHARLIE'S ANGELS
    - ANGEL HUNT. Script dated 6/25/79. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - ANGELS BELONG IN HEAVEN. Script dated 7/21/78. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - CHOPPER ONE
    - KILLING TIME. Script dated 1/21/74. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - CITY BENEATH THE SEA
    - PILOT. Script dated 1/5/68. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - COLUMBO
    - FOOL'S MATE. Script dated 10/24/72. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - COMBAT
    - EVASION. Script dated 6/9/65. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - CRAZY LIKE A FOX
    - IF THE SHOE FITS. Script dated 10/17/85. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - CUSTER
    - DESPERATE MISSION. Script dated 9/1/67. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - D.A., THE
    - PEOPLE VERSUS EDWARDS, THE. Script dated 8/16/71. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - DANGER BAY
    - PRESSURE POINT. Script dated 5/28/86. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - DANIEL BOONE
    - IMPOSTER, THE. Script dated 11/2/67. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - LANDLORDS, THE. Script dated 6/20/69. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - SECRET CODE. Script dated 10/2/67. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - TRAP, THE. Script dated 2/7/66. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - DARKROOM
    - DAISIES. Script dated 10/16/81. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - DEADLINE
    - CRIMES OF PASSION. Script dated 2/1/91. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - DEATH VALLEY DAYS
    - JOLLY ROGER AND WELLS FARGO, THE. Script dated 7/5/66. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - DEFENDERS, THE
    - LITTLE HONOR IS A DANGEROUS THING, A. Script dated 12/26/63. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - DICK POWELL SHOW, THE
    - DAYS OF GLORY. Script dated 2/4/62. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - DORIS DAY SHOW, THE
    - SORROW OF SANGAPUR, THE. Script dated 11/1/71. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - DR. KILDARE
    - HORN OF PLENTY, THE. Script dated 3/8/62. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - DYNASTY
    - EPISODE # 01. Script dated 10/20/80. (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - EPISODE # 02. Script dated 8/4/80. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - EPISODE # 02. Script dated 11/6/80. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - EPISODE # 02. Script dated 11/11/80. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - EPISODE # 03. Script dated 11/19/80. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - EPISODE # 03. Script dated 11/21/80. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - EPISODE # 04. Script dated 12/1/80. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - EPISODE # 04. Script dated 12/2/80. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - EPISODE # 04. Script dated 12/10/80. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - EPISODE # 04. Script dated 8/4/80. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - EPISODE # 05. Script dated 12/8/80. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - EPISODE # 05. Script dated 12/10/80. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - EPISODE # 06. Script dated 12/19/80. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - EPISODE # 06. Script dated 9/15/80. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - EPISODE # 06. Script dated 12/17/80. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - EPISODE # 07. Script dated 1/6/81. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - EPISODE # 07. Script dated 1/2/81. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - EPISODE # 07. Script dated 11/13/80. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - EPISODE # 07. Script dated 12/23/80. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - EPISODE # 08. Script dated 11/24/80. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - EPISODE # 08. Script dated 1/6/81. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - EPISODE # 08. Script dated 1/12/81. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - EPISODE # 09. Script dated 1/21/81. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - EPISODE # 09. Script dated 12/8/80. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - EPISODE # 09. Script dated 1/16/81. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - EPISODE # 10. Script dated 1/2/81. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - EPISODE # 11. Script dated 2/9/81. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - EPISODE # 11. Script dated 2/3/81. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - EPISODE # 11. Script dated 2/5/81. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - EPISODE # 11. Script dated 2/6/81. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - EPISODE # 11. Script dated 2/17/81. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - EPISODE # 12. Script dated 3/5/81. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - EPISODE # 12. Script dated 2/27/81. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - EPISODE # 12. Script dated 2/18/81. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - EPISODE # 12. Script dated 2/9/81. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - EPISODE # 13. Script dated 2/27/81. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - EPISODE # 13. Script dated 2/18/81. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - EPISODE # 13. Script dated 3/4/81. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - EPISODE # 14. Script dated 8/28/81. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - EPISODE # 15. Script dated 9/15/81. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - EPISODE # 16. Script dated 9/14/81. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - EPISODE # 17. Script dated 9/21/81. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - EPISODE # 17. Script dated 9/25/81. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - EPISODE # 18. Script dated 9/30/81. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - EPISODE # 19. Script dated 10/1/81. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - EPISODE # 19. Script dated 10/13/81. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - EPISODE # 20. Script dated 10/14/81. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - EPISODE # 20. Script dated 10/20/81. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - EPISODE # 21. Script dated 11/3/81. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - EPISODE # 22. Script dated 11/11/81. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - EPISODE # 22. Script dated 11/6/81. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - EPISODE # 23. Script dated 11/24/81. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - EPISODE # 24. Script dated 11/27/81. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - EPISODE # 24. Script dated 12/2/81. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - EPISODE # 25. Script dated 12/2/81. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - EPISODE # 25. Script dated 12/7/81. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - EPISODE # 26 - THE HEARING. Script dated 12/16/81. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - EPISODE # 26 - THE HEARING. Script dated 12/29/81. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - EPISODE # 27 - THE IAGO SYNDROME. Script dated 1/4/82. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - EPISODE # 27 - THE IAGO SYNDROME. Script dated 1/11/82. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - EPISODE # 28 - THE PARTY. Script dated 1/19/82. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - EPISODE # 29 - THE BABY. Script dated 1/26/82. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - EPISODE # 30 - MOTHER AND SON. Script dated 2/4/82. (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - EPISODE # 30 - MOTHER AND SON. Script dated 2/1/82. (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - EPISODE # 31 - THE GUN. Script dated 2/16/82. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - EPISODE # 32 - THE FRAGMENT. Script dated 2/26/82. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - EPISODE # 32 - THE FRAGMENT. Script dated 2/24/82. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - EPISODE # 33 - THE SHAKEDOWN. Script dated 3/3/82. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - EPISODE # 34 - THE TWO PRINCES. Script dated 3/19/82. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - EPISODE # 35 - CLIFFS. Script dated 3/26/82. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - EPISODE # 36 - THE PLEA. Script dated 7/2/82. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - EPISODE # 37 - THE ROOF. Script dated 7/8/82. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - EPISODE # 37 - THE ROOF. Script dated 7/13/82. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - EPISODE # 38 - THE WEDDING. Script dated 7/22/82. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - PILOT. Script dated 4/10/80. (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - PILOT. Script dated 11/6/80. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - EAGLE ONE
    - SOMETHING FOR A RAINY DAY. Script dated 9/19/74. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - ELLERY QUEEN
    - ADVENTURE OF COLONEL NIVIN'S MEMOIRS, T. Script dated 8/25/75. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - EMERGENCY
    - PROBLEM. Script dated 7/10/72. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - EXECUTIVE SUITE
    - RE: THE PORNO PLOY. Script dated 7/13/76. (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - RE: THE SERPENT'S TOOTH. Script dated 7/19/76. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - FALL GUY, THE
    - LADY IN GREEN, THE. Script dated 11/14/85. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - FANTASY ISLAND
    - CYRANO/MAGICIAN, THE. Script dated 4/9/81. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - LADIES CHOICE/SKIN DEEP. Script dated 6/16/83. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - LADIES CHOICE/SKIN DEEP. Script dated 6/23/83. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - MOON MADNESS/VAMPIRE. Script dated 11/1/78. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - MOON MADNESS/VAMPIRE. Script dated 11/10/78. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - TALLOWED IMAGE, THE/ROOM AND BARD. Script dated 10/28/82. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - TALLOWED IMAGE, THE/ROOM AND BARD. Script dated 9/30/82. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - TALLOWED IMAGE, THE/ROOM AND BARD. Script dated 10/26/82. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - FBI, THE
    - INSIDE MAN, THE. Script dated 8/28/69. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - FEATHER AND FATHER
    - BIG FRAME, THE. Script dated 7/13/76. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - FIRST AND TEN: THE BULLS MEAN BUSINESS
    - BULLS OWN UP, THE. Script dated 5/11/88. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - FOR THE PEOPLE
    - KIDNAP STORY, THE. Script dated 3/5/65. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - G.E. TRUE
    - CODE NAME: CHRISTOPHER. Script dated 11/15/61. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - GHOST AND MRS. MUIR, THE
    - PILOT. Script dated 11/8/67. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - GHOSTBREAKER, THE
    - GHOSTS IN GLASS HOUSES. Script dated 11/12/64. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - GIRL FROM U.N.C.L.E., THE
    - DANISH BLUE AFFAIR, THE. Script dated 7/11/66. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - GOLDEN GIRLS, THE
    - ACTOR, THE. Script dated 12/3/86. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - HIGH ANXIETY. Script dated 3/8/89. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - GREATEST HEROES OF THE BIBLE
    - STORY OF MOSES AND THE TEN COMMANDMENTS. Script dated 9/16/78. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - GREEN HORNET, THE
    - SILENT GUN, THE. Script dated 7/7/66. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - GUNSMOKE
    - IRON BLOOD OF COURAGE, THE. Script dated 11/23/73. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - HARDY BOYS, THE
    - HOUSE ON DENHAM HILL, THE. Script dated 12/8/77. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - HART TO HART
    - TOO MANY COOKS ARE MURDER. Script dated 3/11/80. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - HAWAII FIVE-O
    - BEAUTIFUL SCREAMER. Script dated 8/20/70. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - CLASH OF SHADOWS. Script dated 9/11/79. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - MURDER--EYES ONLY. Script dated 6/16/75. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - SCHOOL FOR ASSASSINS. Script dated 10/4/79. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - HEC RAMSEY
    - GREEN FEATHER, THE. Script dated 8/14/72. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - HIGHWAY TO HEAVEN
    - REUNION,THE. Script dated 10/26/88. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - HIGHWAYMAN, THE
    - 1945. Script dated 2/17/88. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - HOGAN'S HEROES
    - FUNNY THING HAPPENED ON THE WAY TO LONDO. Script dated 7/14/67. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - HONG KONG
    - CATCH A STAR. Script dated 10/20/60. (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - CLEAR FOR ACTION. Script dated 7/8/60. (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - COLONEL CAT. Script dated 9/26/60. (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - CUPID'S NOOSE. Script dated 11/15/60. (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - DOUBLE JEOPARDY. Script dated 12/19/60. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - DRAGON CUP, THE. Script dated 10/26/60. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - FLIGHT TO NOWHERE. Script dated 8/5/60. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - HAUNTED, THE. Script dated 1/13/61. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - HONG KONG. Script dated 3/17/60. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - INNOCENT EXILE, THE. Script dated 2/21/61. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - JADE EMPRESS, THE. Script dated 8/31/60. (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - JUMPING DRAGON, THE. Script dated 8/17/60. (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - LADY GODIVA. Script dated 12/28/60. (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - LESSON IN FEAR. Script dated 12/5/60. (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - LOVE, HONOR AND PERISH. Script dated 2/9/61. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - MURDER BY PROXY. Script dated 1/20/61. (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - MURDER ROYAL. Script dated 7/20/60. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - NIGHT CRY. Script dated 12/23/60. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - NINE LIVES. Script dated 10/13/60. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - PEARL FLOWER. Script dated 8/25/60. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - PILOT - BLIND BARGAIN. Script dated 7/6/60. (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - RUNAWAY, THE. Script dated 3/7/61. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - SUITABLE FOR FRAMING. Script dated 11/25/60. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - SURVIVOR. Script dated 12/14/60. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - TURNCOAT, THE. Script dated 9/20/60. (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - WITH DEADLY SORROW. Script dated 1/18/61. (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - WOMAN IN GRAY, THE. Script dated 2/7/61. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - HOTEL
    - PILOT. Script dated 3/12/83. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - PILOT. Script dated 3/18/83. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - RALLYING CRY. Script dated 6/17/85. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - TILL DEATH DO US PART. Script dated 11/18/87. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - IRONSIDE
    - SHADOW SOLDIER. Script dated 10/9/72. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - IT TAKES A THIEF
    - CATSPAW. Script dated 1/2/69. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - PROJECT "X". Script dated 2/23/70. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - JUDD FOR THE DEFENSE
    - TRANSPLANT. Script dated 5/27/68. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - KRAFT TELEVISION THEATRE
    - MISS MABEL. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - LEGEND OF JESSE JAMES, THE
    - DEAD MAN'S HAND, THE. Script dated 7/16/65. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - LIEUTENENT, THE
    - WAR CALLED PEACE, THE. Script dated 2/20/64. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - LITTLEST HOBO
    - BOY ON WHEELS. Script dated 6/14/79. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - LOVE BOAT, THE
    - PALIMONYOMINE/FATHER..BEST/'A' FOR GOPH. Script dated 12/10/81. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - WHO KILLED MAXWELL THORN?. Script dated 5/13/86. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - MAGICIAN, THE
    - MAN ON FIRE. Script dated 9/28/73. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - MAMA'S BOY
    - Script dated 4/21/87. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Script dated 4/22/87. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - MAN CALLED SHENANDOAH, A
    - REWARD, THE. Script dated 10/9/65. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - MAN FROM U.N.C.L.E., THE
    - GLITTERING AFFAIR, THE. Script dated 1/15/65. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - SUMMIT-5 AFFAIR, THE. Script dated 7/21/67. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - MANIMAL
    - Script dated 2/22/83. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Script dated 3/8/83. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Script dated 7/14/83. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - MANNIX
    - GIRL WHO CAME IN WITH THE TIDE, THE. Script dated 12/3/68. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - TO QUOTE A DEAD MAN. Script dated 12/7/72. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - MASQUERADE
    - WINNINGS. Script dated 12/5/83. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - MATT HOUSTON
    - BURIED ALIVE. Script dated 2/13/84. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - HERITAGE. Script dated 6/26/83. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - HERITAGE. Script dated 7/10/83. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - HERITAGE. Script dated 7/14/83. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - JOEY'S HERE. Script dated 8/30/82. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - ON THE RUN. Script dated 2/21/84. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - SHARK BAIT. Script dated 9/27/82. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - SHARK BAIT. Script dated 9/21/82. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - MCCLOUD
    - NIGHT OF THE SHARK. Script dated 1/14/76. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - PARK AVENUE RUSTLERS, THE. Script dated 7/19/72. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - MCMILLIAN
    - PHILIP'S GAME. Script dated 8/30/76. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - MEDICAL CENTER
    - PATTERN OF EVIL. Script dated 8/14/69. (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - TAINTED LADY. Script dated 9/11/74. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - MEN FROM SHILOH
    - SIEGE, THE. Script dated 6/15/70. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - MISADVENTURES OF SHERIFF LOBO, THE
    - MYSTERY OF THE ORLY EXPRESS. Script dated 3/5/80. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - MISSION: IMPOSSIBLE
    - DEAL, THE. Script dated 6/29/72. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - TAKEOVER. Script dated 10/20/70. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - MOST WANTED
    - WATERGATE KILLER, THE. Script dated 10/27/76. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - MURDER, SHE WROTE
    - DEADPAN. Script dated 2/26/88. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - TINKER, TAYLOR, LIAR, THIEF. Script dated 1/7/92. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - UNFINISHED BUSINESS. Script dated 7/24/86. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - MY FRIEND TONY
    - VOICES. Script dated 8/28/68. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - NAME OF THE GAME, THE
    - CONSPIRACY. Script dated 5/31/68. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - NEW PERRY MASON, THE
    - CASE OF THE FRENZIED FEMINIST. Script dated 11/12/73. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - OCCASIONAL WIFE
    - DANGER! WOMAN AT WORK. Script dated 7/26/66. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - OUR MAN FLINT
    - ULTIMATUM. Script dated 9/4/75. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - OUTSIDER, THE
    - EYES OF THE BEHOLDER. Script dated 12/31/68. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - PERRY MASON
    - CASE OF THE PROBABLE PROBATIONER, THE. Script dated 9/29/64. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - POLICE STORY
    - CHIEF. Script dated 1/23/74. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - PRIMUS
    - BLACK DIAMONDS. Script dated 7/10/71. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - BLACK DIAMONDS. Script dated 7/6/71. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - RICHARD BOONE SHOW, THE
    - ALL THE BLOOD OF YESTERDAY. Script dated 1/26/64. (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - ALL THE COMFORTS OF HOME. Script dated 7/10/63. (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - ALL THE COMFORTS OF HOME. Script dated 6/26/63. (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - ALL THE COMFORTS OF HOME. Script dated 7/16/63. (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - ARENA, THE. Script dated 1/2/64. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - ARENA, THE. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - CAPTAIN AL SANCHEZ. Script dated 10/4/63. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - DEATHE BEFORE DISHONOR. Script dated 12/19/63. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - DON'T BLOW BUGLES. Script dated 6/18/63. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - DON'T CALL ME DIRTY NAMES. Script dated 8/14/63. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - FIX, THE. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - FLING, THE. Script dated 9/17/63. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - HOOLIGAN, THE. Script dated 11/1/63. (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - MAN ON SPIKES. Script dated 12/9/64. (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - NEED OF VALOR, A. Script dated 2/5/64. (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - NORTH STAR. Script dated 5/16/63. (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - ONE FOR THE MONEY. Script dated 5/22/63. (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - SOROFINO'S TREASURE. Script dated 8/20/63. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - STATEMENT OF FACT, THE. Script dated 6/2/63. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - STRANGER. Script dated 7/16/63. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - TIGER TIGER. Script dated 12/11/63. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - VOTE NO ON 11!. Script dated 9/5/63. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - VOTE NO ON 11!. Script dated 9/23/63. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - WALL TO WALL WAR, THE. Script dated 6/12/63. (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - WELCOME HOME, DAN!. Script dated 9/18/63. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - WHERE DO YOU HIDE AN EGG?. Script dated 8/1/63. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - WHICH ARE THE NUTS AND WHICH ARE THE BOL. Script dated 6/14/63. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - RICHIE BROCKELMAN, PRIVATE EYE
    - Script dated 8/6/76. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - ROOKIES, THE
    - SIEGE. Script dated 10/14/74. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - SAN PEDRO BEACH BUMS, THE
    - LIFTING IS MY LIFE. Script dated 10/13/77. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - SILENT FORCE, THE
    - PROSECUTOR, THE. Script dated 7/13/70. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - SIX MILLION DOLLAR MAN, THE
    - CARNIVAL OF SPIES. Script dated 12/3/76. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - DUEL OF GIANTS. Script dated 1/14/74. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - ENEMIES IN SPACE. Script dated 8/2/77. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - ENEMIES IN SPACE PT.2. Script dated 8/4/77. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - SPACE FAMILY ROBINSON
    - NO PLACE TO HIDE. Script dated 11/17/64. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - STOREFRONT LAWYERS, THE
    - THIS IS JERRY.SEE JERRY RUN?RUN, JERRY.. Script dated 9/4/70. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - SUPERBOY
    - YOUNG DRACULA. Script dated 8/31/89. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - SWITCH
    - SHOOTER FROM TOPEKA, THE. Script dated 9/28/75. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - T.H.E. CAT
    - CURTAIN FOR MISS WINSLOW. Script dated 8/16/66. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - THREE THREE THREE MONTGOMERY STREET
    - PAT AND MIKE. Script dated 12/27/61. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - THRILLER
    - PRISONER IN THE MIRROR, THE. Script dated 4/24/61. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - TIME TUNNEL, THE
    - MOMENT IN THE PAST. Script dated 7/26/65. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - TRAPPER JOHN, M.D.
    - WARNING:I MAY BE HAZARDOUS TO YOUR HEALT. Script dated 11/12/79. (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - WARNING:I MAY BE HAZARDOUS TO YOUR HEALT. Script dated 10/29/79. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - TWELVE O'CLOCK HIGH
    - FORTRESS WIESBADEN. Script dated 5/20/66. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - TWILIGHT ZONE
    - NUMBER 12 LOOKS JUST LIKE YOU. Script dated 9/4/63. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - UNITED STATES STEEL HOUR
    - BITTER SEX, THE. Script dated 11/15/61. (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - MANY WAYS OF HEAVEN, THE. Script dated 2/19/63. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - VEGA$
    - FRENCH TWIST. Script dated 2/20/81. (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - HOOKER MASSACRE. Script dated 11/29/79. (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - YES, MY DARLING DAUGHTER. Script dated 8/24/78. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - VIRGINIAN, THE
    - AS SING VS. WYOMING. Script dated 6/14/67. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - VOYAGE TO THE BOTTOM OF THE SEA
    - DEADLIEST GAME, THE. Script dated 8/11/65. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - FEAR-MAKERS, THE. Script dated 7/30/64. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - FEAR-MAKERS, THE. Script dated 7/21/64. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - WHO'S THE BOSS
    - MONA AND WALTER AND SAM AND ERIC. Script dated 12/7/89. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - WILD WILD WEST
    - NIGHT OF THE PUPPETEER, THE. Script dated 1/10/66. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - YOUNG RIDERS, THE
    - DADDY'S GIRL. Script dated 1/15/90. (Box 14, Folder 7)
- MOTION PICTURES
  - MILLENNIUM (1989)
    - Script dated 2/24/88. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - NEPTUNE FACTOR, THE (1972)
    - unspecified (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - NIGHT MOVES (1975)
    - Script dated 8/28/73. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - STORY OF DR. LISTER, THE
    - Script dated 5/20/63. (Box 23, Folder 10)
- MINISERIES
  - BEST PLACE TO BE, THE (1979)
    - PART I. Script dated 8/31/78. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - PART II. Script dated 8/31/78. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - IMMIGRANTS, THE (1978)
    - Script dated 8/11/78. (Box 26, Folder 3)